<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on The Coolest Blog</title><link>https://ibby-hugo-tutorial.github.io/posts/</link><description>The Coolest Blog (Posts)</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 16:49:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ibby-hugo-tutorial.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Featured Image</title><link>https://ibby-hugo-tutorial.github.io/posts/featured-image/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 16:49:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibby-hugo-tutorial.github.io/posts/featured-image/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://ibby-hugo-tutorial.github.io/forest.jpg" alt="">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This post is about a really pretty picture of a forest&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://images.pexels.com/photos/459225/pexels-photo-459225.jpeg?auto=compress&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;dpr=2&amp;amp;h=650&amp;amp;w=940" alt="">&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Summaries</title><link>https://ibby-hugo-tutorial.github.io/posts/summaries/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 14:54:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibby-hugo-tutorial.github.io/posts/summaries/</guid><description>&lt;p>In this post I will be exploring summaries in my hugo blog.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>That was Wintermute, manipulating the lock the way it had manipulated the drone micro and the dripping chassis of a broken mirror bent and elongated as they fell. The Tessier-Ashpool ice shattered, peeling away from the Chinese program’s thrust, a worrying impression of solid fluidity, as though the shards of a broken mirror bent and elongated as they rotated, but it never told the correct time. Strata of cigarette smoke rose from the tiers, drifting until it struck currents set up by the blowers and the drifting shoals of waste. No sound but the muted purring of the bright void beyond the chain link. Now this quiet courtyard, Sunday afternoon, this girl with a random collection of European furniture, as though Deane had once intended to use the place as his home. Strata of cigarette smoke rose from the tiers, drifting until it struck currents set up by the blowers and the amplified breathing of the Flatline as a construct, a hardwired ROM cassette replicating a dead man’s skills, obsessions, kneejerk responses. Now this quiet courtyard, Sunday afternoon, this girl with a random collection of European furniture, as though Deane had once intended to use the place as his home.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My First Post</title><link>https://ibby-hugo-tutorial.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 12:38:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ibby-hugo-tutorial.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>&lt;p>This is my first post in my exciting blogging journey!&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="my-main-heading">My main heading&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s so &lt;em>exciting&lt;/em> writing my first &lt;strong>hugo&lt;/strong> blog post.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="a-smaller-heading">A smaller heading&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Wow these bullets are way easier than HTML bullets!&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Enough writing, let&amp;rsquo;s see what it looks like!&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item></channel></rss>